# Taoru Huang

#### **Contact**

thbxp@mail.missouri.edu huangtaoru@gamil.com 5738185215 @taoruh

#### Skill

Multimedia Production

Magazine Design

Photography

**News Writing** 

Editing & Proofreading

TV Screenwriting

Outside Broadcasting

Translating & Interpreting

Data Entry

Data Reduction

# Language

#### English

Professional Working Proficiency

#### Chinese

Native Proficiency

### Summary

After diving deep into the mass media industry, I'm currently in a transition towards psychology with a passion for medical care inherited from my parents.

During the past four years I spent in two noted colleges in China and the U.S., my major crossed from Communication to Magazine Journalism (Design), with minor in Psychology. I've accumulated practical skills which range from photography, design to reporting and outside broadcasting.

A combination of media production and mental health care is where my interest locates now. My next step will be psychology graduate schools.

## **Experience**

Designer

Columbia Missourian

August 2019 - Present

Reporter

Columbia Missourian

January 2019 - May 2019

Research Assistant

**MU Peer Relations Lab** 

June 2019 - Present

Research Assistant

**MU Personality Dynamics Lab** 

September 2019 - Present

Columbia, MO

# Outside Broadcasting Staff CUCTV

March 2016 - December 2017

Media Specialist, Assistant Director, Cameraman, Photographer, etc.

Beijing, China

### **Education**

University of Missouri-Columbia Overall GPA 3.6 / Psychology GPA 4.0 Bachelor of Journalism, Magazine Journalism (Design) with Psychology Minor January 2018 - May 2020

#### Communication University of China

GPA 3.6

Bachelor of Arts, Communication September 2015 - December 2017